top of page

* Publisher Solutions
    
* Insights
    
* Еще...

Use tab to navigate through the menu items.

1. Privacy Policy/

##### AdBridg Privacy Policy

Last updated: 2018-05-23

​

​

##### What we collect and why

##### ​

Our website at [adbridg.com](http://adbridg.com/) uses Google Analytics, but we don't collect any other data about you unless you [contact us](http://adbridg.com/contact/) or visit one of our customer's websites.

​

AdBridg licenses technology to Publishers (owners of websites) for the purpose of managing and optimizing their online advertising transactions. This requires us to collect, store, and process data on behalf of our Publishers. They act as Controllers of this data, and we are the Processors.

​

Personal information collected this way includes:

* IP Address
    
* AdBridg Client ID

##### How we collect, use, and share it

##### ​

We use 1st-party and 3rd-party cookies to track the AdBridg Client ID and software performance across multiple pageviews. Your user experience is aggregated into anonymous data so that we can evaluate performance trends and troubleshoot problems. Anonymous data may be shared with 3rd parties at the Publisher's discretion. Your personal data is never shared with anyone other than the Publisher.

​

AdBridg only presents data to Publishers in anonymous, aggregate form. We do not enable Publishers to view specific user sessions, except as required by law enforcement and in cases of internal testing or security investigations. Publishers could request raw log data from AdBridg, however, so please refer to the Publisher privacy policy for details about their use of such data.

​

Raw logs are kept for up to one year. All data is stored and processed in the United States of America.

Further inquiries should be directed to [contactus@adbridg.com](mailto:contactus@adbridg.com).

GDPR Notification

​

If you live within the jurisdiction of EU's General Data Protection Regulation, AdBridg will only store your personal data (IP addresses and AdBridg Client IDs) if the Publisher has provided us with proof of your consent.

##### ​

##### You may have further rights, including:

##### ​

* Right of access to personal data
    
* Right to rectify personal data
    
* Right to erase of personal data
    
* Right to restrict/suspend processing of personal data
    
* Right to complain to a supervisory authority
    
* Right to withdraw consent
    
* Right to data portability

​

To exercise these rights, please submit your request to the Publisher according to the details of their privacy policy.

​

​

###### Streamline your Tech

###### Maximise Revenue

###### Collaborate with Experts

###### Stay ahead of changing Regulations

[Learn how to create an easier path to better ad stack management by receiving best practices, tips, case studies and insights that only ad ops pros care about.](mailto:contactus@adbridg.com)

\>

Thanks!

bottom of page
